# FERNANDA NAUATA Front-End Developer

I have a Bachelor's Degree in Advertising and Marketing and a solid knowledge in working with HTML, CSS, Javascript, Jquery, Bootstrap and currently learning Javascript MV\* Frameworks (i.e. Backbone.js, AngularJS and Knockout). In addition, I have 5+ years of experience as a Graphic Designer and have mastered Adobe Softwares (i.e. Photoshop, Illustrator and InDesign).

Portfolio alvesfernanda.com Linkedin linkedin.com/in/fernanda-nauata

E-mail contact@alvesfernanda.com Skype alves.fernanda2

GitHub github.com/fernandanauata Phone 778.891.4854

# • • • • • • EDUCATION

### UDACITY FRONT-END WEB DEVELOPER NANODEGREE

Learn how to make beautiful, responsive websites optimised for mobile and desktop performance. Get deep in how the web works and gain a working knowledge of the three foundational languages that power websites: HTML, CSS and JavaScript.

#### PART-TIME PROGRAMS, WEB DEVELOPER FOUNDATION

The Web Developer Foundation is a comprehensive part time Certificate program, designed to give a solid foundation in the principles of Web Development. The course is designed to teach the skills, tools and software being used in today's industry.

# ESTÁCIO DE SÁ BACHELOR'S DEGREE, ADVERTISING AND MARKETING

#### ESTÁCIO DE SÁ Brazil | July 2009 - June 2013

September 2016 - in progress

Canada | October - December 2016

**RED ACADEMY** 

# • • • • • • • • •

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### IN SUITS MARKETING Canada | October 2016 - Present

#### WEB AND GRAPHIC DESIGNER

Develop mock-ups and prototypes to effectively communicate interaction and design ideas, promote quality and consistent User Interface and User Experience design. Work on a variety of outputs from web design to print (i.e. Social Media images, brochures, web sites and more).

#### NAUEB DESIGN January 2010 - Present

#### ART DIRECTOR, GRAPHIC DESIGNER

NaUeb is my freelance company through which I have been able to work with clients from differents countries such as Canada, United States, Ireland and others. Additionally, the projects developed consists in visual identities, printed and web advertisements, catalogs, brochures and a number of other services.

#### MKT BRASIL

#### ART DIRECTOR

Brazil | January 2013 - June 2014

My job consisted in developing the overall visual aspects of advertising campaigns and I worked with the team to create a concept and design elements, such as colors and photographs. In addition, some other daily-duties included short-run design projects such as stationery, business cards, brochures, email invitations. Also, I usually talked directly with the clients to receive their feedback and perform any tweaks for ensuring a high quality of the piece before sending it for printing.

#### DOZE

#### ART DIRECTOR

Brazil | September - November 2012

My duties included to set the concept for design projects such as stationery, business cards, brochures, email invitations, and ensure the quality of the files for printing.

#### **MIDIANOVA**

#### GRAPHIC DESIGNER JUNIOR

Brazil | January - October 2012

In this position I assisted Art Directors to print files in the correct format and resolution. After a while I was given more interesting tasks as creating graphic elements where I could show my imagination. For example, I designed stationery, business cards, in-house brochures, email invitations and print ads.